

### CONTACT

**%** +91- 9167054151

□ aadarshk@eng.rizvi.edu.in

ttps://aadarsh-kapoor.netlify.app

### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Python

HTML

CSS

**Javascript** 

jQuery

Adobe XD

С

C++

### PERSONAL SKILLS

- Leadership
- Team Player
- Result Driven
- Effective and Efficient
- English Proficiency- Advanced
- Great Interpersonal Skills

# AADARSH KAPOOR

## SOFTWARE ENGINEER | FRONTEND DEVELOPER | UI/UX DESIGNER

### **ABOUT ME**

Highly motivated Frontend developer along with a knack of UI/UX designing. Love to code and build web pages and applications which are not only beautiful and advanced but also user friendly. Always on the hunt for new designs strategies and emerging technologies. I look forward to obtain an entry-level frontend, UI/UX developer position at a respected organization and utilize the skillset and 2+ years of experience I have to grow and learn everyday.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

USER ENGAGEMENT EXECUTIVE (INTERN) Whitehat jr | Jun 2021 - Jul 2021

Working as an user engagement executive, I made sure the coding syllabus and techniques were conveyed and understood in the best way possible.

TEAM LEAD - SALES (INTERN)
Luminous Studios | Dec 2018 - Feb 2019

Worked as a team lead in sales and achieved my goals using the most efficient and reliable techniques.

### **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING - COMPUTER SCIENCE University of Mumbai | 2018 - 2022 CGPA: 8.24

### AWARDS

- Overall 2nd position in speaking and communication skills award in NCC Army Wing.
- Head of Sports committee in Jr college.
- 1st place in school- SSC board results 2016.
- Head of students council in school.